pixteller.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - PixTeller

PixTeller is founded on the principle of helping people create a huge variety of designs. We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared and we take your privacy very seriously. By visiting the PixTeller website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this [policy](https://pixteller.com/privacy). 

This Privacy Policy covers PixTeller's treatment of personal information that PixTeller gathers when you are on the PixTeller Website and when you use the " **PixTeller services** ". This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that PixTeller does not own or control, or to individuals that PixTeller does not employ or manage. 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 

### Refund policy

You can easily cancel your subscription at any time. There are no cancellation fees, though no refunds are provided for prorated periods. 

We provide refunds in the first 7 days after ordering. 

### Information collected by PixTeller

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our Website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is not compatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our PixTeller users: 

**Information you provide:** We are collecting and store any information you enter on our Website in order to register and use our Service. We are also collecting and processing information you share by contacting the Customer Support only for the purpose to fix any technical or other issues in relation with the Service, to maintain and provide its functionality. You can refuse to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to use certain service or special features. 

**Registration information:** When you register to PixTeller we ask you to provide certain personal information, including a valid email address, location and username. We may collect additional information such as physical address and additional authentication information, to provide you with the services you need (such those that require payments), or to ensure the marketplace integrity (for example, prevention of fraud). We collect information to provide better services and enhanced user experience to all of our users. In addition, we collect information while you access, browse, view or otherwise use the Website. In other words, when you access the Website we are aware of your usage of the Website, and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, including geo-location information, IP address, device and connection information, browser information and web-log information, and all communications recorded by Users through the Website. We use that information to enhance user experience, personalize your browsing experience as well as monitor the Website for fraud and inappropriate content or behavior. We may also collect supplemental information obtained from third parties such as demographic and navigation data. Once you register, your username and additional information regarding your activity that you choose to make public on the Websitte will be visible to all Users of the Website. This information includes photos you upload, your published portfolio, ratings, and additional information you may choose to add to your profile as public. In case you choose to connect to PixTeller by using your account information from other platforms such as Facebook, Google Plus, we are going to collect the information for which you have consented to share that can allow you to access our Service. You can always unlink the your third party account and we will never collect such information. 

**User Profile:** Beside the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information, such as favorite URLs. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. These information is optional and you may choose not to share it with us. 

**Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. PixTeller and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, PixTeller cookies information, and the page you requested. PixTeller uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. 

**Links:** PixTeller may keep track of how you interact with links in posts across our Services including third party services and clients by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on. This type of information is anonymized and the scope is to improve the service. 

### How do we collect Information?

You directly provide us with most of the information we collect. You do this by filling out the [registration](https://pixteller.com/signup) details on the Website, and by posting and sharing additional information voluntarily. This can include information like user's location (but not GPS location), sharing of the designs you create, ratings, feedbacks and anything you choose to add to your user profile and make public. 

We also collect technical information indirectly and automatically through our systems. This information may include logging your Internet Protocol (IP) address, software configuration, operating system and use of cookies (cookies are small files sent from us to your computer and sometimes back). Cookies ultimately help us improve your navigation and ease of use of our Website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. You can find further information about Cookies in this policy below. 

### How do we use the Information collected?

We use personal information only as appropriate to provide you with quality service and security. For example, we may use the information collected from you to verify your identity. We may also use this information to establish and set up your account, verify or re-issue a password, log your activity and contact you from time to time. The information helps us improve our services to you, customize your browsing experience and inform you about additional products, services or promotions from PixTeller that may be of interest to you. In addition, this information helps us track any fraudulent activities and other inappropriate activities and monitor content integrity. Should you ever deactivate your account with us, we will keep your information on file, but only use it to comply with regulatory requirements and to contact you occasionally with the option to reactivate your account only if we have your consent in doing so. 

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those set out in this privacy policy. We process personal information on our servers in different jurisdictions worldwide. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country in which you live, but make sure it will comply with Data Protection requirements. Currently our servers are in European Union. 

We retain information as long as it is necessary and relevant for our operations. In addition, we may retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce our [Website Terms](https://pixteller.com/terms) and take other actions permitted by law. 

### Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. 

We may combine your personal information with information we collect automatically or obtain from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can opt-out through the link attached to each communication or by sending an email to us. 

We may provide your personal details to third parties, only in order to operate the Website, and prevent fraud and illegal activities, as detailed below:  
\- to service providers for the purpose of opening, operating and servicing your account (example - payment vendors, CRM systems, mailing systems or technical consultants);  
\- to respond to a subpoena or court order, judicial process or to regulatory authorities;  
\- to protect against fraud, unauthorized transactions (such as money laundering), claims or other liabilities. 

We do not collect credit information; but allow our payment vendors to collect information for the purpose of collecting the payments for the service provided on the Website. We are not exposed to the payment information provided to our payment vendors, and this information is subject to the privacy policy applicable to the payment vendor. 

### PixTeller and Cookies

PixTeller uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information, but not personal data such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, but about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to the users. 

Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor, use DART cookies. These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

### Cookies and Localstorage

When you visit our Website, we may use industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer and which will allow us, among other things, to enable automatic sign-in to the Website, make your browsing much more convenient and effortless and allow us to test user experience and offer you personalized browsing or promotions. Cookies (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are text files that help store user preferences and activity. 

The Website uses cookies to collect statistical data about its use, to tailor the Website's functionality to suit personal preferences and to assist with various aspects of Website operation. These files contain a variety of information such as information about web pages visited by you, the length of time you visited certain sites, data about how you came to visit particular sites, the scope and nature of those sites, areas viewed by you, and additional information. These cookies do not collect or use personal information about the users. 

**Blocking Cookies:** You may set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it's important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, cookies may, in certain cases, save you from the need to enter usernames and passwords, and allow session continuity. 

### Third Party Websites

While using the Website you may encounter links to third party websites. PixTeller is not responsible for these sites and has no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the [Terms of Service](https://pixteller.com/terms) or service of such websites. Our terms of use and our privacy policy apply only to information collected by us in accordance with this policy. 

### Email Communications

PixTeller is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission. You may receive notification e-mails from PixTeller, which inform you of actions that have been performed on the site or system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

### Keeping Information Secure

Your PixTeller account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. 

Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

We take great care in maintaining the security of the Website and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through industry standard technologies and internal procedures. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. In case of a breach that will affect your data, we are going to notify you with undue delay. 

Users who have registered to the Website agree to keep their password in strict confidence and not disclose such password to any third party. 

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. 

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please [contact us](https://pixteller.com/contact). 

### Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at "[www.PixTeller.com/privacy](https://pixteller.com/privacy)". If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

### Your rights under GDPR

If you are an EU citizen you are governed from a Privacy point of view by GDPR rules. 

**Your rights under GDPR are:**  
\- Access your information  
\- Update your information  
\- Request the deletion of your information (the right to be forgotten)  
\- Object to the use of certain personal information  
\- Request access restriction to your information  

For exercising any of the above rights, you can contact us directly. You have also the right to form a complaint to the Data Protection Authority in case you are concerned about a violation of your rights in relation with your personal information or if we are not able to resolve your request.   

For more details related to your personal information used by PixTeller, you can always write us [here](https://pixteller.com/contact). 

### Your consent and contact information

By using the PixTeller Services and our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our [Terms of Service](https://pixteller.com/terms). PixTeller may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Feel free to contact us anytime and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. If you have additional questions, feel free to [contact us](https://pixteller.com/contact).
